corkcicle.com 2017-05-20

# Privacy Policy – CORKCICLE.

## Privacy Policy.

Hewy Wine Chillers, LLC (“CORKCICLE”) is committed to respecting the privacy of all visitors to our Web site. The following policy describes how we collect, protect and use information we receive. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, our use of your information, or if you would like to change how we communicate with you, email [info@corkcicle.com](mailto:info@corkcicle.com)

### What information does Corkcicle collect and how does Corkcicle use it?

Corkcicle collects several types of information on our Web site. We collect personal information based on information that you provide when you request to receive email, newsletters or other products or services from us. We use this information to ensure you receive the correct products and services in a timely manner. If you have purchased from us or subscribed to one of our newsletters and have chosen to receive email from us, we may occasionally update you via email of special opportunities. If you prefer to not receive this information, or would like to opt-out of any other communication, simply use the unsubscribe link provided in the email.

We will not rent or sell your name, address, email address, credit card information or personal information to any third-party without your permission. However, we must cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer.

To customize the information you wish to receive from us, or to let us know you do not wish to receive email from us, simply notify us of your email preferences. We may share non-personal, non-individual statistical or demographic information in aggregate form with our marketing partners, advertisers or other third parties for research purposes.

### Third-party links:

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third-party links on our site. However, we have no control over these linked sites. Each of these sites has its own separate and independent privacy, data collection policies and practices. Corkcicle is not responsible or liable for the content of these linked sites, as they are provided for your convenience and are to be accessed at your own risk. We do, however, seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about external links, including information regarding a broken link.

### Your consent:

By using the Corkcicle.com website, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy:

We will change, amend and update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in our privacy practices, technology, products and services, general business operations and industry. In the event of any such change, we will post a revised policy on this Web site and revise the “Last Updated” date of such policy. We reserve the right to change, amend and update this Privacy Policy at any time in our sole and absolute discretion, and such changes will be effective upon posting of the revised policy. In the event of a material change in our information collection and use practices, we will provide more prominent notice of such change along with the revision to the effective date of the policy. You should check this Privacy Policy on a regular basis to ensure you have reviewed and are familiar with the most current policy. Contact us for any questions or concerns you may have regarding this Privacy Policy and our information and data collection and use practices. Please email [info@corkcicle.com.](mailto:info@corkcicle.com)

### Terms of Use:

The purpose of this site is to learn about products offered by Hewy Wine Chillers, LLC (DBA – Corkcicle), purchase these products for personal use, or learn how to contact Corkcicle for other manners related to partnerships in retail or distribution.

Corkcicle has the right to cancel, refund, and/or not fulfill any orders placed on this site for any reason, at any time. Corkcicle strictly prohibits the resale of product purchased on this site (www.corkcicle.com) for resale on any other third party websites or retail outlets. Any violation or perceived violation of this policy warrants Corkcicle the full right to cancel and refund, without fulfilling the order, upon any suspicious behavior that is believed to be a violation of this policy.

#### Last Updated 2014-08-25
